So now let's talk about Amazon Bedrock.
So Amazon Bedrock is the one service on AWS.
They're going to use to build generative AI applications.
So it's very powerful and it allows you through an interface to play with many models
and configure them in order to get the outcome you want.
So it's called a fully managed service that means that for you,
there is no service into managed.
You just use the service on AWS and Amazon Web Services will make sure
that the service is working for you.
So you're going to keep control of all the data you're going to use to train the model
because it all happens within your account.
It never leaves your accounts.
You're going to have a paper use pricing model
but we'll go into the pricing model later on as well.
There's a unified API so that means that to access Amazon Bedrock
and the many models behind Amazon Bedrock,
you only have one way of doing it which is standardized.
You can leverage a wide array of foundation models.
We'll have a look at them in a second and on top of it,
you have advanced features such as RAG or LLM agents
and you get security, privacy, governance and responsible AI features as well
within Amazon Bedrock.
So we're going to spend a bit of time learning about it
and practicing together.
So what type of foundation models do we have access to on Amazon Bedrock?
Well, many companies have agreements with AWS to publish their models on Bedrock.
So we have AI21 Lab, we have cohere,
we have stability AI, we have of course Amazon themselves,
we have anthropic, meta, and of course over time,
more foundation models and more companies behind these models
are going to be added into Amazon Bedrock.
So the way it works that whenever you use one of these models,
Amazon Bedrock is going to make a copy of the foundation model, the FM,
and it's going to be only available to you.
And then in some cases, you're going to be able to use your own data
to fine tune the model to your needs.
Again, you need to know that none of your data
is going to be used and sent back to one of these providers
to train the foundation model.
What you get happens all within your account and only within your accounts.
So it's always helpful to get a diagram to understand a service.
So I mean one for Amazon Bedrock.
So we have at the center of it foundation models.
And those are the ones we've seen and we'll have a look in the hands-on
to see how we can select them.
And we're going to have an interactive playground
that we're going to have a look at it as well in the next lecture
in which, as a user, we're going to select a model we want to use.
And then we're going to start asking questions to the model, for example.
What is the most popular dish in Italy?
And then maybe the playground is going to respond pizza and pasta.
On top of it, this is just for the basic interactions,
but we can have also knowledge bases or rag.
And we'll have a full lecture dedicated to this.
So don't worry if you don't understand it right now.
But the idea is that we're going to be able to provide more relevant
and more accurate responses by fetching data from external data sources
that may have the answer for us.
Don't worry, we'll have a deep dive into knowledge bases as well.
We can fine tune our foundation model.
That means that we're going to bring our own data
and we're going to update the foundation model in our account again
with our data to make sure that it's more adapted to our use case
and our data.
And finally, to access all of these things is going to be a unified API.
So it's going to be the same for all models.
That means that all your applications
just took in one way to Amazon bedrock
and then Amazon bedrock will do the magic for us.
So that's it for this lecture.
I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture
for some practice on Amazon bedrock.